<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Achievements. on Hi, I&#39;m Igor.</title>
    <link>https://example.com/achievements/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Achievements. on Hi, I&#39;m Igor.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 12:41:46 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/achievements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bp Global STEM Academies.</title>
      <link>https://example.com/achievements/bpglobalstem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 12:41:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/achievements/bpglobalstem/</guid>
      <description>You can click here to see more photos!
Brief summary: In july 2019, I was awarded a one month full STEM scholarship in Cairo, Egypt, as part of a colaboration between AFS and BP. While there, I visited many universities and laboratories, while also taking classes in mathematics, physics and chemestry.
The program aims to select students between 15 and 17, who have great interest in STEM, and want to create impact in their communities, with interdisciplinary thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CERN - Advanced Physics.</title>
      <link>https://example.com/achievements/cern/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 12:41:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/achievements/cern/</guid>
      <description>Brief summary: Throughout 2018, 2019 and 2020, I took advanced physics classes at my school.
We studied topics such as elemental particles, basics of particle acceleration, physics of light and other forms of radiation.
Many researchers also gave talks, as part of the program. Among them, were people from CBPF (Brazilian Center of Physics Research) and UFRJ (one of the most prestigious academic institutions in Brazil).
In 2019, as the culmination of the program, the study group visited CERN, the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest particle accelerator, in Switzerland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OBI - Finalist in Brazil&#39;s National Olympiad in Informatics</title>
      <link>https://example.com/achievements/obi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 12:41:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/achievements/obi/</guid>
      <description>Brief summary: Throughout 2020, I competed in all phases of OBI, Brazil&amp;rsquo;s National Olympiad in Informatics.
As the results for the finalist phase have yet to annouced, the certificates too are not yet available - and will be displayed in the awards and certificates page once they are released.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Osciloscope Music Talk</title>
      <link>https://example.com/achievements/osciloscope/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 12:41:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/achievements/osciloscope/</guid>
      <description>In the end of 2019, I got to talk a bit about two topics that are very dear to me. Physics, and music. Through the lens of &amp;ldquo;Osciloscope Music&amp;rdquo;, I present many different physics concepts in acoustics, while weaving the narrative around fun drawings and music history. Although the talk was given in Brazilian Portuguese, there are subtitles available.
  Some of the topics and questions covered in the video:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STEM Tutoring and Classes.</title>
      <link>https://example.com/achievements/stemtutoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 12:41:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/achievements/stemtutoring/</guid>
      <description>Brief summary: Since 2018, I&amp;rsquo;ve been giving private tutoring lessons on math, physics and chemestry to other students and peers. Also in 2018, I started teaching classes on these subjects, on school after-hours.
As my interest in teaching grew, I started to search for more opportunities to share and learn. In 2020, I started teaching math classes at a community driven non-profit organization, that helps students from lower socio-economic standpoits get into their desired universities, through extremely low-cost classes with volunteer teachers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zewail City Micro-Biology Course.</title>
      <link>https://example.com/achievements/zewailcity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 12:41:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/achievements/zewailcity/</guid>
      <description>Brief summary: While in Cairo (through AFS, in 2019), I also took a course on microbiology and water treatment cycles. The week-long program had us sleeping in the universitie&amp;rsquo;s dorms, and featured many interesting experiments and demonstrations. Many of the experiments were directly involved in the process of water treatment, like purification, ph treatments and others. Additionaly, we had lessons regarding virology and bacteriology, my favorite being the experiments with E.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
